There's so much text in today's world, pretty much none of us have enough time to
在如今的世界，文字信息如此之多，我们几乎没有足够的时间
read all the things we wish we had time to.
阅读所有我们希望有时间阅读的所有内容。
So one of the most exciting applications I've seen of large language models is to use it
因此，我见过的大型语言模型最令人兴奋的应用之一就是将其用于
to summarize text.
对文本进行总结。
And this is something that I'm seeing multiple teams build into multiple software applications.
这是我看到的许多团队将其整合到多个软件应用中的功能。
You can do this in the ChatGPT web interface.
您可以在ChatGPT网络界面中执行此操作。
I do this all the time to summarize articles so I can just kind of read the content of
我一直在使用这个功能来总结文章，这样我就可以
many more articles than I previously could.
比我以前能阅读的更多文章的内容。
And if you want to do this more programmatically, you'll see how to in this lesson.
如果您想以更编程化的方式执行此操作，您将在本课中了解如何操作。
So that's let's dig into the code to see how you could use this yourself to summarize text.
那么让我们深入代码，看看您如何自己使用此功能来总结文本。
So let's start off with the same starter code as you saw before of import OpenAI,
那么让我们从之前看到的相同的起始代码开始，导入OpenAI，
load the API key and here's that get completion helper function.
加载API密钥，这里有一个获取补全的辅助函数。
I'm going to use as the running example, the task of summarizing this product review.
我将以总结这个产品评论为例来演示。
Got this panda plush toy for my daughter's birthday, who loves it and takes it everywhere,
我为女儿的生日买了这只熊猫毛绒玩具，她非常喜欢并且带着它到处去，
and so on and so on.
等等等等。
If you're building an e commerce website, and there's just a large volume of reviews,
如果您正在建立一个电子商务网站，并且有大量的评论，
having a tool to summarize the lengthy reviews could give you a way to
拥有一个可以总结冗长评论的工具可以让您
very quickly glance over more reviews to get a better sense of what all your customers are thinking.
快速浏览更多评论，更好地了解您的所有客户在想什么。
So here's a prompt for generating a summary.
所以这里有一个用于生成摘要的提示。
Your task is generate a short summary of a product review from e commerce website, summarize
您的任务是从电子商务网站的产品评论中生成简短的摘要、总结
review below, and so on, in at most 30 words.
以下评论等等，最多用30个词。
And so this is soft and cute panda plush toy loved by daughter, but small for the price,
所以，这是一只受到女儿喜爱的柔软可爱的熊猫毛绒玩具，但价格有点小贵。
arrived early.
提前到货。
Not bad.
还不错。
It's a pretty good summary.
这是一个相当好的总结。
And as you saw in the previous video, you can also play with things like
正如您在之前的视频中看到的，您还可以尝试
controlling the character count or the number of sentences to affect the length of this summary.
控制字符数量或句子数量以影响摘要的长度。
Now sometimes when creating a summary, if you have a very specific purpose in mind for
有时在创建摘要时，如果您心中有一个非常具体的目的，
the summary, for example, if you want to give feedback to the shipping department, you can
例如，如果您想向运输部门提供反馈，您可以
also modify the prompt to reflect that so that they can generate a summary that is more
修改提示以反映这一点，以便他们可以生成更
applicable to one particular group in your business.
适用于您业务中的某个特定群体。
So for example, if I add to give feedback to the shipping department, let's say I change
例如，如果我要向运输部门提供反馈，我们假设我修改这里
this to start to focus on any aspects that mention shipping and delivery of the product.
开始关注提到产品运输和交付的任何方面。
And if I run this, then again, you get a summary, but instead of starting off
如果我运行这个，那么您再次得到一个摘要，但是不是从
with soft and cute panda plush toy, it now focuses on the fact that it arrived a day earlier than expected.
柔软可爱的熊猫毛绒玩具开始，现在关注的是它比预期提前一天到达。
And then it still has other details.
它仍然有其他一些细节。
Or as another example, if we aren't trying to give feedback to the shipping department,
或者，作为另一个例子，如果我们不是要向运输部门提供反馈，
but let's say we want to give feedback to the pricing department.
但我们假设我们想要向定价部门提供反馈。
So the pricing department is responsible for determining the price of the product.
所以定价部门负责确定产品的价格。
And I'm going to tell it to focus on any aspects that are relevant to the price and perceived value.
我将告诉它关注与价格和感知相关的任何方面的价值
And this generates a different summary that it says, maybe the price may be too high for a size.
这会生成一个不同的摘要，可能对于尺寸来说价格过高，
Now in the summaries that I've generated for the shipping department or the pricing department,
现在，在我为运输部门或定价部门生成摘要，
it focuses a bit more on information relevant to those specific departments.
它更关注与这些特定部门相关的信息。
And in fact, feel free to pause the video now and maybe ask it to generate information
实际上，现在随时暂停视频，也许请它生成信息
for the product department responsible for the customer experience of the product or
关于负责产品的客户体验的产品部门或
for something else that you think might be interesting to an e-commerce site.
关于您认为对电子商务网站可能有趣的其他事物。
But in these summaries, even though it generated the information relevant to shipping, it had
但是，在这些摘要中，即使生成了与运输相关的信息，它还具有
some other information too, which you could decide may or may not be helpful.
一些其他信息，您可以决定是否有帮助。
So depending on how you want to summarize it, you can also ask it
因此，根据您想要如何总结它，您还可以要求它
to extract information rather than summarize it.
提取信息而不是总结它。
So here's a prompt that says you're tasked to extract relevant information
因此，这里有一个提示，表示您的任务是提取相关信息
to give feedback to the shipping department.
向运输部门提供反馈
And now it just says, product arrived a day earlier than expected without all of the other
现在它只是说，产品比预期提前一天到达，而没有其他的
information, which was also helpful in a general summary, but less specific to the shipping
信息，这在总体摘要中也很有帮助，但对运输来说不太具体
department if all it wants to know is what happened with the shipping.
部门如果它只想知道运输发生了什么。
Lastly, let me just share with you a concrete example for how to use this in a workflow
最后，让我与您分享一个如何在工作流程中使用此功能的具体示例
to help summarize multiple reviews to make them easier to read.
帮助总结多个评论，使其更易于阅读。
So here are a few reviews.
这里有一些评论。
This is kind of long, but here's a second review for a standing lamp, need a lamp on the bedroom.
这有点长，但这是一个落地灯的第二个评论，卧室需要一个灯
Here's a third review for an electric toothbrush.
这是一个电动牙刷的第三个评论。
My dental hygienist recommended.
我的牙科卫生师推荐。
Kind of a long review about the electric toothbrush.
关于电动牙刷的一段较长的评论。
This is a review for a blender when it said, so said 17 piece system on seasonal sale and
这是关于搅拌机的评论，当它说，所说的17件套系统在季节性销售
so on and so on.
等等等等。
This is actually a lot of text.
这实际上是很多文字。
If you want, feel free to pause the video and read through all this text.
如果你愿意，请随时暂停视频并阅读所有这些文字。
But what if you want to know what these reviewers wrote without having to stop and read all
但是，如果您想知道这些评论者写了什么，而无需停下来阅读
this in detail?
这些详细信息？
So I'm going to set review one to be just the product review that we had up there.
所以我将把第一条评论设置为我们之前的产品评论。
And I'm going to put all of these reviews into a list.
然后我要把所有这些评论放到一个列表里。
And now if I implement a for loop over the reviews.
现在，如果我对这些评论实现一个循环。
So here's my prompt and here I've asked it to summarize it in at most 20 words.
这是我的提示，我要求它用最多20个词来总结。
Then let's have it get the response and print it out.
然后让它获得响应并打印出来。
And let's run that.
然后运行它。
And it prints out the first review is that PandaToy review, summary review of the lamp,
它打印出第一条评论是关于PandaToy的评论，关于灯的总结评论，
summary review of the toothbrush, and then the blender.
关于牙刷的总结评论，然后是搅拌机。
And so if you have a website where you have hundreds of reviews, you can imagine how you
所以，如果你有一个网站上有几百条评论，你可以想象如何
might use this to build a dashboard to take huge numbers of reviews, generate short summaries
使用这个来构建一个仪表板，处理大量评论，生成简短的摘要
of them so that you or someone else can browse the reviews much more quickly.
这样你或其他人可以更快地浏览这些评论。
And then if they wish, maybe click in to see the original longer review.
如果他们愿意，可以点击查看原始更长的评论。
And this can help you efficiently get a better sense of what all of your customers are thinking.
这可以帮助您更高效地了解您所有客户的想法。
All right, so that's it for summarizing.
好了，总结就到此为止。
And I hope that you can picture if you have any applications with many pieces of text,
我希望你能想象，如果你有任何包含大量文本的应用，
how you can use prompts like these to summarize them to help people quickly get a sense of
你可以如何使用这些提示来总结它们，帮助人们快速了解
what's in the text, the many pieces of text, and perhaps optionally dig in more if they wish.
文本中的内容，许多片段，如果他们愿意，也许可以选择深入了解
In the next video, we'll look at another capability of large language models, which is to make
在下一个视频中，我们将了解大型语言模型的另一种能力，即进行
inferences using text.
使用文本进行推理。
For example, what if you had, again, product reviews and you wanted to very quickly get
例如，如果你再次有产品评论，你想要迅速了解
a sense of which product reviews have a positive or a negative sentiment?
哪些产品评论具有积极或消极的情感？
Let's take a look at how to do that in the next video.
让我们在下一个视频中看看如何做到这一点。